LABEL,ABBR,CAP,LOC,POS,POS+1,POS-1,PREF,SUFF,WORD,WORD+1,WORD-1
B-LOC,0,1,1,NNP,NN,PHIPOS,0,0,Israel,television,PHI
O,0,0,0,NN,VBD,NNP,0,0,television,rejected,Israel
O,0,0,0,VBD,DT,NN,0,0,rejected,the,television
O,0,0,0,DT,NN,VBD,0,0,the,skit,rejected
O,0,0,0,NN,IN,DT,0,0,skit,by,the
O,0,0,0,IN,DT,NN,0,0,by,the,skit
O,0,0,0,DT,NN,IN,0,0,the,comedian,by
O,0,0,0,NN,NNP,DT,0,0,comedian,Mr.,the
B-PER,1,1,0,NNP,NNP,NN,0,0,Mr.,Tuvia,comedian
I-PER,0,1,0,NNP,NNP,NNP,1,0,Tuvia,Tzafir,Mr.
I-PER,0,1,0,NNP,OMEGAPOS,NNP,0,0,Tzafir,OMEGA,Tuvia
O,0,1,0,IN,NNP,PHIPOS,0,0,During,Security,PHI
B-ORG,0,1,0,NNP,NNP,IN,0,0,Security,Council,During
I-ORG,0,1,0,NNP,VBP,NNP,0,0,Council,game,Security
O,0,0,0,VBP,NNP,NNP,0,0,game,Tuesday,Council
O,0,1,0,NNP,NN,VBP,0,0,Tuesday,night,game
O,0,0,0,NN,IN,NNP,0,0,night,after,Tuesday
O,0,0,0,IN,DT,NN,0,0,after,the,night
O,0,0,0,DT,NNP,IN,0,0,the,U.S.,after
B-LOC,1,1,0,NNP,NN,DT,0,0,U.S.,6th,the
B-ORG,0,0,0,NN,NNP,NNP,0,0,6th,Fleet,U.S.
I-ORG,0,1,0,NNP,VBD,NN,0,0,Fleet,played,6th
O,0,0,0,VBD,.,NNP,0,0,played,.,Fleet
O,0,0,0,.,OMEGAPOS,VBD,0,0,.,OMEGA,played
